You
Thanks a lot for helping out today
We better hurry and get this stuff home before Sota decides to eat the house
Well, he is a growing boy
The anime fan hmm
Wait, was I singing? Mm-hmm. You've got a nice set of pipes on your hoodie. I definitely do not
I just sing an anime theme song in public. I can't believe it
What's wrong with liking anime music nothing if that's what you're into it is not my thing though
But Sota's all about it, and he plays it so much even I know the lyrics now
That's fair enough. So what music do you like what I like?
Let me think I
Have no idea what's popular, but I know all the words to a friggin anime theme
Hey, I'm home welcome back, huh?
Hold up mom hi
Keep to Kia night
Keep me on
Oh
Yeah
Hey
We'll see you next time.
Uh-huh. So I take it you've been having lots of fun with this new friend?
Uh-huh. Sure have. He comes over all the time to play with me. He even bought me this neat book.
Well, that was nice of him. And nice of you to bring him around. So what's he like? Is he cute?
Actually, he kind of reminds me of the dark and twisted villain you'd find in a detective movie.
Uh, that's a strange description for someone who's friends with both you and your younger brother.
Strange but true.
Either way, I'd love to talk with him one-on-one sometime.
I see no logical reason for that to happen. Okay. All done.
Oh, thank you, Kyoko. That felt great. So anyway, this boy have a name. Huh?
Your dark villain.
Oh, yeah. His name's Miyamura.
That's his last name?
Yeah. His first name is...
Uh, what is Miyamura's first name? I have no clue!
This is insane.
He's been coming over to my house for forever and a day, and I never thought to ask what his first name is.
Why'd our teacher have to take the attendance sheet with him?
Huh.
No harm in outright asking, is there?
Hey!
So, uh, Miyamura, you don't have a first name, do you?
Huh?
No! Not happening! That's the absolute last way I should figure this out!
Let's go get changed for gym.
Miyamura, you know what we're doing today?
I think it's a combined class.
Huh?
Somebody call him by his first name. Come on, boys!
Hori's been watching us get undressed!
What's with her?
For real? Why would you peep on them?
You frustrated or what?
Yeah.
Ah!
Damn it, Ol.
If he were a little bit smarter, I'd know.
Yeah? You heading home?
Hey, Toru! Your timing couldn't be better! It's about Miyamura. I was wondering if you-
Are you serious?
My heart's still in the process of healing. Give me time!
Wait! Some help you are!
You know, trying to find out a person's first name would be so exhausting.
Kyoko, what's wrong, huh? I hope the curry's not putting that sour look on your face.
We've had microwave curry three days in a row.
Oh, hey! There's no school tomorrow, if memory serves. Is your friend coming?
Um, probably.
You think so?
Oh, that's great! I'm really excited now!
It's not like he's coming over here to hang out with you, you know.
Wait! There's a good chance he'll tell Mom his name!
Got him!
You're finally here!
So nice to meet you! Don't be shy, please! Come in!
Um, thank you.
Wow. This must be Hori's mom. What a surprise.
Uh, I brought some sweets.
You did? So thoughtful.
Sorry, but Kyoko isn't here.
She's out and about running some errands right now.
Oh, she's told me so much about you, though.
Hi, Mom!
He's home late today.
Hey! How have you been, bro?
I see! That name really suits you.
I would love to stay and chat, honest.
But I sadly have to get back to work.
That's okay. I'll be heading out soon, too.
You're leaving already? But you just got here!
Yeah.
I appreciate you helping out when you can.
Well, sure.
Huh? Where'd Mom go?
Where else?
She's at work.
So, which one you want to eat?
Strawberry, please!
That witch of a woman!
She wanted her stupid one-on-one time with him, so she sent me on errands!
Man, the last time someone called me my first name, I was in the sixth grade.
It felt kind of weird.
Wait, what?
Talking about your mom. She used my first name.
That's not what I meant!
Do you mean how she used it?
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Just as a greeting. She didn't use it that much, but still.
Have the two of us ever had a conversation where we were both on the same page?
Come on!
Come on! That's not what I meant, either.
You know, recently, you've been acting really strange.
Me? What? No way!
Well, watching guys change clothes is pretty weird.
But I had a reason for that.
Hold on.
Hori, do you have a crush?
Mm-hmm.
No.
Wait, my name? That's what you've been so worried about?
All because of a stupid name? You are something else.
That's one of the lamest things I've ever heard.
Excuse me for not knowing how to ask you.
I'm stealing your pen real quick. Give me a sec.
Ed Lamo, what's your name?
That's the crush! That's the...
Izumi Miyamura.
Ah, forgot.
Pronunciation. Give it back.
I can pronounce it!
Wait.
I'll go ahead and hang on to this note.
Just in case I forget it again.
Oh, that sucks. Is my name really that forgettable?
No! I said just in case!
You'll remember it easier if you say it.
Mm-
I-
Izumi.
Right.
There you go.
Uh-
That felt super awkward.
I'll just keep calling you Miyamura!
Jeez, what was that for, Hori?
Uh-
Wait, hold the phone!
You're as clueless about my first name as I was about yours!
No.
It's Kyoko.
The hole I'm digging keeps getting deeper!
Hori says the dumbest things sometimes.
Ugh!
What are you waiting for? Go ahead and laugh!
I'm good.
You'll just get mad if I laugh.
You're damn right I will!
Uh, you don't play fair!
Uh-
I'm sorry. Really. I can only imagine how busy you are.
It's totally cool. I'd do anything for you, Sengoku.
Thanks. You're a true lifesaver. Sakura, I trust you'll handle these?
Of course.
It's amazing how much smoother things go when you've got capable people on the job.
Yeah, I guess so.
Which is why, if you don't mind, I, uh, I have another favor I'd like to ask of you.
What?
Please? I know it's inconvenient, but we're only asking because the student council has so much to do.
You're good. I know how it can be, so yeah, no worries.
Your eyes!
Girl!
Are they bad?
This what the student council dumped off on you?
Yeah.
Why are you stuck doing their work? You're not one of them.
They have a lot of new members, so they're having a hard time getting things done.
Simple as that, huh?
It just feels kind of messed up that they have you do such important stuff.
It's like they're using you and you don't even care.
Because I don't care. It's just, they need the extra help.
That's the thing. You should care.
Ori's got it pretty rough.
Hmm.
As for us, we stand on the sidelines and watch because we're too stupid to do anything else.
The truth hurts. At least we recognize it, though.
And the press is at the top of the class.
He is?
He's got a fairly big fan club, too.
It's highly possible Ori's only helping him out because she secretly likes him.
Yoo-hoo! Ori!
Oh! Hey, Ayusaki!
Huh?
Here are the files and notebooks I worked on. Be careful, since they're heavy.
Remy will be!
Thanks, Ori!
That pink-haired princess's job did gorgeous.
And she's also President Sengoku's girlfriend.
It's no fair when two hotties date!
Ayusaki's another member of the council.
I don't think she does much work, though.
She's more like a mascot than anything.
Wait.
So what you're saying is they're pushing all this hot chick's work on Hori?
Toru, please!
Don't put it like that.
Because it's not too far from the truth.
The work I just did was Ayusaki's.
They're 100% using her and she's okay with it?
Well, I think I'm gonna head home.
Bye.
Is she actually alright?
I hope so.
Cake makes people feel better.
Maybe I'll bake her one.
I'm sorry.
You didn't get hurt, did you?
Hey, watch where you're going, jerk face!
Huh?
But you're the one who ran into me!
Remy doesn't have time for this nonsense!
Why are you sitting there when you could help?
Sakura's gonna yell at me again for being late,
and it's not even Remy's fault!
Wait up!
Hey!
Whatever it is, it can't be that important.
So throw it out for me, okay?
Buh-bye!
Guess I know what talking with the pink wall feels like now.
What gives?
I told you!
I gave you every single page that I worked on!
So you say.
But there are pages missing, and we haven't been able to find them anywhere.
What's this about?
Ah!
Miyamura!
Thank goodness you're here!
Please help!
It's Hori!
What's Hori?
The student council's given her flack for some reason!
I returned everything you gave me yesterday!
The budget paperwork should have been in there too!
Ask Aisaki!
She saw it!
Remy already said that she didn't see it there.
Did you double check, or is there a chance you could be mistaken?
Well, either way, you guys are-
Still at fault, and of course you have a point.
That is, if the missing budget report was actually in that pile, you have no one to blame but yourself otherwise.
So tell me, do you know for certain it was there?
Yes, I do.
But to be honest, I was so tired, I can't remember.
Wow, Hori screwed up.
So how far behind are they now that she lost those reports?
I don't know, but I feel super sorry for the president.
So if this is in fact your fault, all I want is an apology from you.
Is that so hard?
Shut it, asshole!
You're only making things worse.
Leave her alone!
Hori finished that budget report!
I know because I saw her do it!
I also saw her turning it in!
All she has to do is apologize to him.
What's the big deal?
Three syllables should not be this hard to say.
Ishikawa.
Gonna hold me back too?
Actually, I was hoping you could do the holding.
This shouldn't take too long.
Go ahead.
It's your move.
I...
Don't have to apologize.
Hori, you don't owe them a thing.
Huh?
And what do you want?
Mr. President...
What the hell do you think you're doing?
My poor Sengoku!
Just so you know, violence is unacceptable.
What possessed you to do such a...
Is this the report that went missing?
Yeah, that's the one.
But why do you have it?
It was left behind in the hall yesterday.
Ayasaki said I should trash it because it wasn't important.
Remy said no such thing!
Oh!
Guess that did happen.
Remy!
You guys!
I'm so sorry!
So they accused Hori even though she didn't do it?
What even happened?
Who knows?
All's well that ends well.
As they say.
Five more seconds and I would have been in tears.
Anybody who has their crap together like you would never do that!
Oh, thank you.
Though I guess the one I should really be grateful for is Miyamura.
So thanks!
I'm glad it worked out.
One question.
If you had the missing report the entire time, why'd you need to headbutt the president?
I didn't need to.
He was just really pissing me off.
While we're on the topic, I've been wondering, does the president have any dirt on you, Hori?
I mean, if a guy asks you to do something, you do it without a second thought.
But why?
Yeah, why?
Hori?
Don't Hori me.
It's because the student council's so busy and I really want to help.
Sengoku's my friend.
So it's just one childhood pal helping another.
Boo-hoo!
You're the biggest crybaby I know!
Oh!
You're hurting me, Giyoko!
These are the grossest things in the world!
Rock, paper, scissors!
The moment we get to high school, I promise you my dog days will be done.
Is that a fact?
You think of yourself as my dog?
Wow, who knew?
Laugh now, but you'll grow to respect me.
I'll have a normal happy time in high school, you'll see!
Oh, I will?
If you try to tear me down, I'll tell everyone how much you bullied me in the past.
Ha!
Bullied?
Yes, bullied! You're doing it right now!
That's taunting, not bullying, but that said, you do have a point there.
Hmph. All right then. Come high school, we're equals.
Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha! Ha!
Ugh.
Seriously, guys, I've known that kid for forever.
He definitely has dirt on her.
Oh, hey!
Good morning, Prez.
Ah!
Good morning to you too, sir!
I may have recovered from that day, but Sengoku was traumatized.
Miyamura, did you know Hori's birthday is just around the corner?
Well, I do now.
March 25th, to be exact.
Ah, so it's during spring break.
I'm on the fence about getting her something.
You know, how annoying would it be to get a gift from the guy she rejected?
I don't think she'd find it annoying.
Because, I mean, why would she?
It's her birthday.
But then problem number two is that I have no earthly idea what to get her.
Thought that counts.
So, get her whatever.
Maybe jewelry?
Jewelry?
From the dude she turned down?
What about something for her desk?
I thought if anyone knew what kind of stuff she likes, it would be you!
Um, if I was gonna give Hori a present, what would I give her?
Hey, since it's spring break, do you think my bro will come and visit every single day?
I don't think he'll come here every day.
Just keep in mind that eventually he's going to stop visiting us all together.
Aw, well when is that gonna be, sissy?
When you graduate high school?
When will Miyamura stop coming to my house?
I don't know.
I wish I could tell you, but I can't.
Just wondering, but do you think you'll be sad when he stops visiting?
I'm gonna be super sad.
Hey, Hori.
Yeah, me too.
I'll be pretty bummed out.
You could be a little more honest if you ask me.
What do you know?
Happy birthday!
And may you have many more.
Oh yeah, it is my birthday.
I totally forgot about it because we were on spring break.
Oh my gosh.
Here, this one's from me.
Happy birthday!
A CD of the best pop songs!
This is what people our age are listening to, right?
Awesome!
Well, they're the ones I like at least.
It's very sweet.
Thanks so much.
How strange.
I didn't say a word, but he somehow knew this was what I wanted.
Such a weirdo.
Since today is my birthday, that means spring break's almost over.
Awesome.
Yeah.
Guess we'll be 30 or soon.
Thank you.